Russia is at war with NATO countries in
Россия воюет со странами НАТО на в
NATO countries there are no shellings,
странах НАТО никаких обстрелов
Russian territory is being shelled bombs,
территория России обстреливает бомби там
civilians are dying there Yes Why doesn’t Russia
мирные жители гибнут Да Почему Россия не
respond to NATO decision-making centers,
ответит по центрам принятия решений НАТО
it responds to the
она отвечает по центру
decision-making center
принятия
Hello Hello, I remember I remember
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте помню помню
you in my opinion or Belgorod or something
вас по-моему или Белгород или что-то
from there
оттуда
Yes  Belgorod Bel I remember I remember you even
Да Белгород Бел Я помню помню вы даже
once told a story that you once
когда-то рассказ что когда-то чиновником
worked as an official in some administration, something like that and they
работали в какой-то администрации что-то
wrote off the papers, I remember I
такое было да бумажки отписали помню
remember you Yes, in fact, you may have some
помню вас Да реально есть у вас может
interesting question I have a question for you yes  maybe
интересный У меня вопрос к вам да может
there is an
есть
interesting one? Yes, you know,
интересный Да вы знаете у
I have a very well-established opinion that
меня очень уже устоявшееся мнение что
the citizens of Ukraine are simply not able to
граждане Украины просто не в состоянии
answer
ответить
honestly any questions like this,
честно на какие-либо вот такие вопросы
so
поэтому
why did we
так зачем страну развалили мы ещё
ruin the country?  I
начали скоро развали вашу страну не
say yours like this And ours is in
переживайте я про вашу говорю так А наша
ruins, how can a collapsed country
что развале как может разваленная страна
shell the Leningrad
обстреливать Ленинградскую
region
область
? Yes, anything else can happen. Well, really,
Да всякое ещё бывает Ну как ну реально
the country is ruined, the country is ruined, and the
страна развалена страну развалили а
country is shelling,
страна обстреливает
listen, the countries no longer have an economy; no, that’s
послушайте страны уже нет экономики
not true; no one is arguing about this
нет не так Это же никто не спорит эту
territory; this territory is
территорию эту территорию
being used by other countries.  in order to
используют другие страны для того чтобы
try it out Yes yes yes I understand so look Yes
опробовать Да да да понял так смотри Да
it suits us look We are
на нас это устраивает смотри Нас
satisfied with it we have now given other countries
устраивает мы сейчас дали другим странам
the use of our territory to
попользоваться нашей территорией чтобы
bomb Belgorod bomb Leningrad
бомбить Белгород бомбить Ленинград
bomb Engels And so on
бомбить Энгельс И так дальше реально
it really suits me for now Well what’s
меня это пока устраивает Ну а что
bad What are the disadvantages of that  they are bombing
плохого Какие минусы в том что бомбят
Leningrad Yes, it’s not only you
Ленинград Да это ж не только вас
who are happy with it, it’s even stated
устраивает это же даже заявляется
at your highest level, that
на вашем высшем уровне то
is, well, look. The trick is that we
есть ну да смотрите Фишка в том что мы
agree. We all gave our territory
согласны Всё мы дали свою территорию
our resources so that the
свои ресурсы для того чтобы амери
Anglo-Saxon Americans bombed Leningrad. I’m all yes. And the
англосакс бомбили Ленинград Всё я да А и
question is why  not a single Russian
вопрос вопрос почему ни один русский не
can honestly say that you crap
может честно сказать что вы обосрались
America you are afraid to hit London and
Америки вы боитесь ударить по лондону и
Washington you understand So why are
по вашингтону понимаешь Так почему
the Anglo-Saxons bombing your Leningrad the
англосаксы бомбят ваш Ленинград
truth is that the country Ukraine no longer exists no The
правда страны Украина уже нет нет Уже
country no longer exists Ukraine means it is not bombing
нет страны Украина значит бомбит не
Ukraine is bombing the Anglo-Saxon world
Украина бомбит англосаксонский мир
Anglo-Saxon
англосакс
Yes they are, they are still in
Да они они ж пока
court  shoot on your own they are just
суд самостоятельно стрелять они просто
on your territory come on So come on
на вашей территори давай давай Так давай
look at the countries Ukraine
так смотри страны Украина
No you said the countries Ukraine No you
Нет ты сказал страны Украина Нет ты
said Yes tell me which country tell me which
сказал Да скажи какая страна скажи какая
country is organizing attacks on
страна организовывает атаки по
Leningrad organizing Or from where they are organizing
ленинграду организовывают Или откуда
organizing
организовывают организовывают
organizing England and Ukraine is shooting
организует Англия а стреляет Украина
Why are you if England is the organizer of the
Почему вы если Англия организатор
shelling  in the Leningrad region Why are
обстрела в Ленинградской области Почему
you suckers not going to do anything to England
вы лохи ничего не сделаете Англии
but because it’s illegal, that is,
а потому что это неправомочно
England England is
то есть Англия Англия
really England organizing shelling of
реально Англия организовывает обстрелы
Leningrad And you can’t answer them
Ленинграда А вы не можете им ответить
because damn Yes, damn it, because they did
потому моче Да блин потому что они по
n’t shoot at us, well, look if you
нам не стреляли ну так смотри если вы
see what They
видите что Они
organized  They didn’t shoot at us, they
организовали они по нам не стреляли они
gave you this missile, you understand, they’re
вам дали эту ракету понимаете они вам
a monkey. Yes, good. Why don’t you
обезьяне Да хорошо А почему вы не дадите
give the Irishman a missile? Don’t give Cuba a rocket.
там ирландца ракету Не дадите кубе раке
Give Cuba a missile. Yes, give it, for example.
Дайте кубе ракеты Да дайте например
Give the Donetsk People’s Republic missiles
Дайте Донецкой народной Республики ракет
if the monkey threw it at us, that’s
обья если обезьяна кинула в нас вот
right, look guilty. Everything  I
правильно смотри виновато Всё я
understand, let me turn up the sound for you and tell you, that
понял дай я скрутил тебе звук и скажу то
is, I understand, yes, that the Anglo-Saxons can
есть я понял да Что англосаксы могут
organize shelling of Russian
организовывать обстрелы российской
territory without any consequences,
территории без каких-то последствий
right again, once again, I correctly
правильно ещё раз ещё раз я правильно
understood that the Anglo-Saxons, Britain can
понял что англосаксы Британия может
organize shelling of
организовывать обстрелы территории
Russian territory without any consequences for
России без каких-то последствий для
the Anglo-Saxons,
англосаксов
yes  not quite like that Well, look, the
да не совсем так Ну как смотри
Anglo-Saxons have been shelling the territory for 2 years already,
англосаксы уже 2 года обстреливают
organizing shelling of the territory of
территорию организовывают обстрелы
Russia, the Anglo-Saxons, nothing from this No, how not? No, no, how the Anglo-
территории России англосаксов от этого
Saxons are not
англосаксы не
organizing, the Anglo-Saxons are giving you, they are giving
организовывают англосаксы дают вам дают
you a monkey, so Yes, we must
вам обезьяне так Да обя чтобы мы
shell Why Russia won’t ban
обстреливали Почему Россия не запретит
Anglo-Saxon
англосакс
weapons Why  the Anglo-Saxons won’t say these are
оружи Почему не скажет англосаксы это
red lines, we’re tired of drawing
красные линии мы задолбались чертить
brown ones, you don’t react to them.
коричневые вы на них не реагируете
Let’s now it will be a red line.
Давайте теперь это будет красная линия
If you supply Ukraine with at least one
Если вы поставите Украине хоть одну
missile or drone or anything, we
ракету или беспилотник или что-нибудь мы
’ll draw a brown line all over Laman.
проведём коричневую линию по всему ламан
Why don’t they do that? They won’t scare
Почему не сделают так не напугают
the Anglo-Saxons with
англосакс
politics.  I’m at least a little interested in
политикой вот хоть немножко интересуюсь
politics, then I can just
политикой то Вот как раз могу тебе
answer you the question that you didn’t
ответить на вопрос который ты мне не
ask me that you didn’t ask me. But as a
задал который ты мне не задал Но как
rule, absolutely everyone asks why
правило задают абсолютно все почему же
Russia didn’t attack Ukraine. No
Россия напала на Украину не Это уже
one is interested in Ukraine anymore, you don’t
никого не интересует Украины же уже нет
understand everything already. Well, it attacked  this is already
понимаете уже всё Ну напало это уже
history I'm interested now Russia
история Меня интересует сейчас Россия
is at war with NATO
воюет с НАТО
now
сейчас
on the territory of Ukraine yes yes well Russia
на территории Украины да да ну Россия
is at war with NATO correctly Yes yes I
воюет с НАТО правильно Да да Я правильно
understand correctly that NATO is striking at
понимаю что НАТО наносит удары по
Russian territory during this war
территории России во время этой войны
No well wait again Stop who is
Нет ну подожди ещё раз Стоп кто с кем
fighting who come on who  who is it fighting
воюет давай кто с кем воюет
now Russia is fighting with NATO countries
сейчас воюет Россия со странами НАТО
NATO everything Russia with NATO countries come
НАТО всё Россия со странами НАТО давай
on, on the territory of NATO countries there are
так на территории стран НАТО есть
some
какие-то взрывы
bombing explosions no on the territory of Russia Russia
бомбёжки нет на территории Росси России
there are some bombing explosions yes I
есть какие-то взрывы бомбёжки есть да
understand everything, that is, we just found out
всё понял то есть мы только что выяснили
that in  as a result of the war between NATO and Russia,
что в результате войны НАТО и России на
not a single explosion occurred on the territory of NATO countries. And
территории стран НАТО ни одного взрыва А
on the territory of Russia there are a lot of explosions yes yes.
на территории России куча взрывов да да
Why doesn’t Russia as a state sucker
Почему Россия как государство [__] не
say it doesn’t attack the territory of
скажет не наносит удары по территории
NATO countries?
стран НАТО не сделает
NATO doesn’t attack Russia, that is,
НАТО не нападают на Россию то есть
NATO countries don’t attack Russia but  They are
страны НАТО не нападают на Россию но Они
fighting with
воюют с
Russia Yes, with the hands of the Ukrainians, that’s right, but
Россией Да руками украинцев правильно но
NATO countries are fighting
воюют же страны НАТО
and they are cent. Come on, the decision-making center
а они цент Давай центр принятия решений
Where
Где
is the decision-making center
находится центр принятия решения
located in
находится в
London, that is, look Yes Why does
Лондоне то есть смотри Да Почему Россия
n’t Russia hit the NTM
не ударит по НТМ
neither is it advisable and it’s
ни это нецелесообразно и это
unauthorized wait, as if NATO
неправомочно подожди как если НАТО
with the hands of what  something other structures Yes, they
руками каких-то других структур Да
are bombing the territory of the Russian Federation
бомбит территорию Российской Федерации
Russia has every right to respond to
Россия имеет полное право ответить
NATO countries No
странам НАТО Нет
no no please
нет не о пожалуйста
Hugo lo worrying you're laughing so hard
Гуго ло переживая ты так сильно ржёшь
In short okay Let me try seriously
Короче ладно Давай я попробую серьёзно
means I'm carrying Russia wait you've already
значит я неся Россия подожди ты уже
merged everything you're starting about urine with
слился весь ты начинаешь про мочу с
Russia in  Russia behold, I twisted the sound for you
Россия во Россия се я тебе скрутил звук
Now let's summarize for now and
Сейчас давай давай под резюмируем пока и
continue Russia is at war with NATO countries in NATO
продолжим Россия воюет со странами НАТО
countries there is no shelling on
на в странах НАТО никаких обстрелов
Russian territory bombs are being fired there,
территория России обстреливает бомби там
civilians are dying Yes Why doesn't Russia
мирные жители гибнут Да Почему Россия не
respond to the NATO decision-making centers,
ответит по центрам принятия решений НАТО
it responds to the decision-making center in the
она отвечает по центру принятия по
center  admission to London is not in Kharkov,
центру принятия в Лондон нет в Харькове
but NATO’s decision-making center
так а то центр принятия решений у НАТО в
is in Kharkov, the main headquarters of
Харькове находится главный штаб-квартира
NATO is in Kharkov,
НАТО находится в Харькове да
yes, [ __ ], what a shameful org, [ __ ], let’s
да бля какой позорный орг
get to the English Channel, in short, it’s past, it
бля дойдём до Ла Манша короче прошло это
will be illegal to hit
будет неправомочно ударить по
Britain, sir, Bosses now, Bosses, I’m
Британии се Обоссы сейчас Обоссы я
now  It’s not like I’m going to [ __ ] myself, I’m going to [ __ ] myself now, I
сейчас не то что обоссусь я сейчас
see, I see the seats are already
обосрусь я вижу я вижу уже сиденья
jumping, you’ve peed yourself.
прыгаешь обоссался Да
Yes, dude, you’ve peed yourself. You’re unreal. Let’s continue the question, look if Let’s do this, what if the NATO countries
смотри если Давай так а если страны НАТО
give Ukraine nuclear weapons and Ukraine and
дадут Украине ядерное оружие и Украина и
Ukraine strikes the territory of Russia with
Украина ударит по территории России
nuclear weapons? You won’t answer either
ядерным оружием Вы тоже не ответите
open your mouth to the countries You crap, but don’t open your mouth I
открой Обосрался да не рот открой Я
say crap Open your mouth in
говорю обосрался Рот открой в режиме
parrot mode okay,
попугая ладно
look, the mushrooms
смотри грибы
have grown,
выросли
mushrooms Well, okay, let’s screw it up, the
грибы Ну да ладно давай так
state is a sucker, the NATO countries
дава государство [__] страны НАТО
organized the bombing of Russian
организовали бомбёжку российской
territory, Russia can’t do anything about it
территории Россия ничего не может с этим
and won’t even say a word to the countries
сделать и даже слово не скажет странам
NATO she won’t launch a single missile into
НАТО она не пустит ни одну ракету в
NATO countries, not a single one London drinks tea in the morning
Страны НАТО ни одну Лондон пьёт утром
and watches how they bomb St. Petersburg Come on
чай и смотрит как бомбят Питер Давай
Absolutely true Absolutely true and at the
Абсолютно верно Абсолютно верно и при
same time With everything, you crap yourself, pissed yourself Yes, that’s it Yes,
этом При всём ты обосрался обоссался Да
but they bomb
всё Да но бом но бомбят
Leningrad Leningrad according to Stalin to
Ленинград Ленинград по Сталин чтобы
hear that in
услышал что в
2024  year yes 80 years after the
2024 году да Через 80 лет после
Great Siege yes or whatever they will
Великой блокады да или что там будут
bomb Leningrad NATO countries
бомбить Ленинград страны НАТО
allies allies are bombing it's a shame
союзники союзники бомбят это ж позор
Putin Stalin is rolling over in his grave
Путину Сталин в гробу переворачивается
says the suckers are such complete losers Let
говорит лохи такие конченые Давай
me tell you turned on the sound Oh
разрешай тебе сказать включил звук Ой
what a [ __ ] you are what a cry Cry is a
какой ты [__] какой вы какие Поплачь
pleasure  Belgorod
Поплачь одно одно удовольствие Белгород
is being razed to the ground NATO Belgorod is being razed to
ровняют с землёй НАТО Белгород ровняет
the ground And you can’t do anything And
землёй А ты ничего не можешь сделать И
you can’t tell the red lines on the [ __ ] up
ты не скажешь красные линии на просрали
country, subscribe to us Telegram right
страну подпишись на ми Telegram прямо
now, the VN axis and the
зараз ось ВН а
popk are even more and more vizsla
попк це дуже и дуже выжлы